Hello, Pied Piper!
Reasoning in LLM’s and its role in Agenetic Systems 
This module tell us about the Evolution and Reasoning Understanding In LLM’s.
The method by which LLMs process their thinking logically by dividing each processes into chunks and try and act as a humans for solving the problem, the pattern how they memorize and respond. How they dynamically make predictions between weights and biases to give a humanised response. 

The evolution of reasoning in LLM is done by training the modules on a large number of datasets, as such feeding a baby with all the knowledge in the world for get the inhuman ability.

As reasoning plays an important role in making the agentic systems as they due to their critical role in the environment, their actions not only takes the input of one parameter but it conclude all sorts of information before taking action.

The module also explains about the ReACT-based model tuning uses a framework for tunning agents with more reasoning and thinking faster than earlier responses.using this framework, it makes the agent more efficient and  think better before committing to any actions.






